{"version": "1.0", "categories": {"Corporate identity - branding": [{"question": "What does \"USP\" mean?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Unique Selling Proposition"}]}, {"question": "Define \"Perceived Quality\".", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Perceived quality describes the Quality the customer perceives including the emotional connection to the product (image and design) as well as the multi-sensory sensation. "}]}, {"question": "List 3 criteria your logo should fit!", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Refelct your company in a unique and honest way."}, {"index": 2, "text": "Contain a symbol which is relate to your industry, your name, a defining charactereistic of your company or a competitive advantage you offer."}, {"index": 3, "text": "Work in black and white as well as in colour."}, {"index": 4, "text": "Be scalable."}, {"index": 5, "text": "Be symmetric."}, {"index": 6, "text": "Have a closed and clear shape."}]}, {"question": "How is the brand awareness determined.", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "The brand awareness is determined trough surveys of different targetgroups (exp. first thought on a picture)."}]}, {"question": "What are the four parts of a brand?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Perceived Quality"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Brand Awareness"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Brand Loyalty"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Brand Association"}]}, {"question": "Name three parts of the corporate communication.", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Advertising"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Pubic relations"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Information"}]}, {"question": "Which properties influence the brand assosiation (name at least 2)?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Colour"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Country of origin"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Heritage"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Other brands"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Consumers and not consumers of a brand"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Rating"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Sponsoring and popular advertiser"}]}, {"question": "Define the \"Corporate Identity\".", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "A corporate identity is the overall image of a corporation, firm or business in the minds of diverse publics, such as customers, investors and employees."}]}, {"question": "What is a trademark?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "A trademark is a name, logo or symbol which expresses uniqueness."}]}, {"question": "Explaine the four parts of the branding pyramid with the example of a car.", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Attribute level / Core benefit - drives you from A to B"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Functional benefit - drives you fast and secure from A to B"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Emotional benefit - gives you a sporty, aesthetic and nice ride"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Endbenefit - drivin to delight"}]}, {"question": "Name 2 external factors of the corporate identity?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Market"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Economy"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Government policy/legislation"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Competitors"}]}, {"question": "Name 2 parts of the corporate design.", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Logos"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Uniforms"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Corporate colours"}]}, {"question": "What is a brand?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "It encompasses how you manage your customer relationships and how you are perceived as a business."}]}, {"question": "List five properties on the USP?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 5, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "ability to defence"}, {"index": 2, "text": "orientation to audience"}, {"index": 3, "text": "economic feasibility"}, {"index": 4, "text": "price"}, {"index": 5, "text": "quality"}, {"index": 6, "text": "special features"}]}, {"question": "Define \"USP\".", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Real or perceived benefit of a good or service that differentiates it from the competing brands and gives it buyer a logical reason to prefer it over other brands."}]}, {"question": "List at least 2 parts of the branding pyramid?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Attribute level / Core benefit"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Functional benefit"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Emotional benefit"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Endbenefit"}]}, {"question": "Name one part of the corporate behaviour.", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Internal values"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Internal norms"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Internal \"rules\""}]}, {"question": "What are the three parts of the corporate identity?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Corporate design"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Corporate communication"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Corporate behaviour"}]}, {"question": "Define \"Brand Loyality\".", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Brand Loyality descripes the customers purchasing behaviour (example rebuying)."}]}, {"question": "Your logo should not... (list 2 criterias)!", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "be to detailed."}, {"index": 2, "text": "be to complex."}, {"index": 3, "text": "be overdrawn."}]}, {"question": "What are the five internal factors of the corporate identity?", "status": "approved", "category": "Corporate identity - branding", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 5, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Staff"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Production Capacity"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Operating cash reserve"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Location"}]}], "Economics": [{"question": "A situation of several requestors and several suppliers is also called a bilateral [...].", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Oligopoly"}]}, {"question": "True or False?\n\"Create maximum output with minimum input\" describes the optimumprinciple.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "True"}, {"index": 2, "text": "False"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Falsch"}]}, {"question": "Economics is a ...", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Natural Science"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Jurisprudence"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Cultural Science"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 3, "text": "Kulturwissenschaft"}]}, {"question": "Which of the following points applie to a capitalistic marked?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "The decision making is decentralized"}, {"index": 2, "text": "The decision making is centralized"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Die Entscheidungsstrucktur ist dezentral"}]}, {"question": "List 3 aspects of corporate behaviour.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Financial management"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Employee management"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Tone"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Reaction to criticism"}]}, {"question": "Name two kinds of markets.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Job market"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Key market"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Capital market"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Procurement market"}]}, {"question": "Which entries stand on the passiv side of the balance sheet?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Fixed assets"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Current assets"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Equity"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Borrowing"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 3, "text": "Eigenkapital"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Fremdkapital"}]}, {"question": "List 2 finacial decision criteria.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Liquidity"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Profitability"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Chance-/risk-balance"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Independence / dependence"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Sustainability & social responsability"}]}, {"question": "What is a franchise?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "A franchise is a cooperation of two parties where one party is the giver and the other party is the taker of the rights to deliver services and goods of a specific brand."}]}, {"question": "List 2 principles of a social marked (e.g. Germany).", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Garanty of social equality"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Income distribution in favor of financialy vulnerable people"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Social insurance"}]}, {"question": "Which kind of accounting handels the loans and advances to customers?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Finance accounting"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Receivable accounting"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Payable accounting"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Asset accounting"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Wage accounting"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Inventory accounting"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Debitorenbuchhaltung"}]}, {"question": "Which of the following shares are ordinary shares?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Bearer shares"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Registered shares"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Vinkulated shares"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Voting benefits"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Dividend benefits"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Advantages of the liquidation proceeds"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Inhaberaktien"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Namensaktien"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Vinkulierte Aktien"}]}, {"question": "What is a balance sheet?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "A balance sheet is a statement of the assets, liabilities, and capital of a business or other organization at a particular point in time, detailing the balance of income and expenditure over the preceding period."}]}, {"question": "Costs, which can not be directly assigned to a single cost object (product), e.g. packing kost, shipping cost storageor appraisal costs, are part of the [..]", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Indirect material costs"}]}, {"question": "What does funding mean?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Funding describes the origin of capital."}]}, {"question": "What does investment mean?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Investment describes the use of funding."}]}, {"question": "What is equity?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Equity is capital that gives the capital giver rights but is not backed"}]}, {"question": "What does SME's stand for?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Small and medium enterprises"}]}, {"question": "Name three needs of a human being.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Basic needs"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Security"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Sozial needs"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Appreciation"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Individual fulfilment"}, {"index": 6, "text": "WLAN"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Physiological needs"}]}, {"question": "Trying to get the most out of a given input describes the [...].", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Maximum principle"}]}, {"question": "What is the synonyme for a household?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Consumption economy"}]}, {"question": "Which of the following investments is impact related?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Property investment"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Finance investment"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Intangible investment"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Net investment"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Reinvestment"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Gross investment"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Hierarchy related investment"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 4, "text": "Net investment"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Reinvestment"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Gross investment"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Hierarchy related investment"}]}, {"question": "Which of the following investments is object related?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Property investment"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Finance investment"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Intangible investment"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Net investment"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Reinvestment"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Gross investment"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Hierarchy related investment"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 3, "text": "Immaterielle Investitionen"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Finanzinvestitionen"}, {"index": 1, "text": "Sachinvestitionen"}]}, {"question": "What is the term for absolute competition?\n", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Polypoly"}]}, {"question": "What is mezzanine capital?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Mezzanine capital is a hybrid of debt and equity capital that gives the lender the rights to convert to an ownership or equity interest in the company."}]}, {"question": "If you distinguish goods from their place in the transformation process, they are categorized in [...]?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Input- and outputgoods"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Capital and consumption goods"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Material and immaterial goods"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Input- und Outputg\u00fctern"}]}, {"question": "What is the synonyme for a business?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Production industry"}]}, {"question": "Jewelry, a second flat or a luxury car are all [...].", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Luxury needs"}]}, {"question": "How many requestors are there in a so called Monopsony?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "One"}, {"index": 2, "text": "A few"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Many"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "one"}]}, {"question": "What is the break even point?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "The break even point is the point in time the revenue exceeds the expenditure"}]}, {"question": "Wherefor do you need scarce commodities?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Satisfaction of needs"}]}, {"question": "Into which parts are production costs split up?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Production overhead"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Production wages"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Depreciation"}]}, {"question": "Aiming to achieve the desired results with minimimum input is also called [...]?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Minimum principle"}]}, {"question": "List 2 pricing mechanisms.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Const-oriented pricing"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Marked-oriented pricing"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Demand-oriented pricing"}]}, {"question": "Air, sun and water can also be called [...].", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Free goods"}]}, {"question": "What is an affiliated group?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "A group of indipendent companies which are working together."}]}, {"question": "What kind of output good is a hardback book in a printing office?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Unfinished product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Finished product"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Internal labour"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Commodity"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Fertiges Erzeugnis"}]}, {"question": "List 4 aspects of corporate design.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Logo"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Colors"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Uniforms"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Letter Heads"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Business cards"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Online presence"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Architecture of coporate buildings"}, {"index": 8, "text": "Acoustic presence"}, {"index": 9, "text": "Corporate smell"}]}, {"question": "What is economic action?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "The systematic use of given goods and services."}, {"index": 2, "text": "To optimize for maximum profit"}, {"index": 3, "text": "To invest into the best stock."}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Bestehende G\u00fcter und Dienstleistungen planvoll einzusetzen."}]}, {"question": "How can you categorize goods? Name two.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Property rights"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Availability"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Satisfaction of needs"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Quality"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Physical properties"}]}, {"question": "Rare goods are also called [...]", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Economic goods"}]}, {"question": "What is pretended self-employment?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Pretended self-employment discribes the situation, in that a self-employed person is working for a company in a manner that allows the conclusion that this person is an employee but is not paying social insurance fees a normal employee would pay."}]}, {"question": "What kind of good is paper in a stationary shop?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Unfinished product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Finished product"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Internal labour"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Commodity"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 4, "text": "Konsumgut"}]}, {"question": "What is another name for an unfinished product?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Semi-finished product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Interim result"}]}, {"question": "What kind of good is printed but loose paper in a printing office?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Unfinished product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Finished product"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Self labour"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Commodity"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Gebrauchsgut"}]}, {"question": "In which two kinds are production costs split up?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Material costs"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Manufacturing costs"}]}, {"question": "Into which kinds are the material costs split up?\n", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Materials overhead"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Prodcution material"}]}, {"question": "Are food, clothes and accommodation basic needs?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Yes"}, {"index": 2, "text": "No"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Nein"}]}, {"question": "List 3 privileges of a shareholder.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Participation in the general assembly"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Right to vote"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Right of dividend"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Portion of liquidation revenue"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Option on new stock"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Right for information"}]}, {"question": "Which kind of accountig handels the liabilities towards suppliers?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Finance accounting"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Receivable accounting"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Payable accounting"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Asset accounting"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Wage accounting"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Inventory accounting"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 3, "text": "Payable accounting"}]}, {"question": "What kind of of good is a drill in a household?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Consumer goods"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Consumables"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Capital good"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Gebrauchsgut"}]}, {"question": "What is a corporate vision?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "The corporate vision is the long term basic idea of the direction a company is heading"}]}, {"question": "Name four stakeholders", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Government"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Competitors"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Clients"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Invetors"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Suppliers"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Managers"}, {"index": 7, "text": "Employees"}]}, {"question": "Which entries stand on the active side of the balance sheet?", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Fixed assets"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Current assets"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Equity"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Borrowing"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Current assets"}, {"index": 1, "text": "Fixed assets"}]}, {"question": "List 2 aspects of corporate communication.", "status": "approved", "category": "Economics", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Communication (internal and external)"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Advertising"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Public relations"}]}], "Marketing- Product": [{"question": "What does the actual product consist? (List 5 things)", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 5, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Packaging"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Features"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Brand name"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Quality"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Product mix"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Design"}]}, {"question": "What does the core benefit consist?", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "It consists of the problem-solving services or core benefits that consumers obtain when they buy a product."}]}, {"question": "Define \"Product\".", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "A product is anything that can be offered to a market, that might satisfy a want or need."}, {"index": 2, "text": "Products consist of anything that can be marketed"}]}, {"question": "What does the augmented product consist?", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 3, "text": "Warranty and services"}]}, {"question": "What are the six important aspects about naming your product/business/website?", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 6, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Be easy to pronounce and spell."}, {"index": 2, "text": "Be memorable."}, {"index": 3, "text": "Do not be to specific in naming"}, {"index": 4, "text": "No negative connotations "}, {"index": 6, "text": "Make sure your name does not alienate any group "}, {"index": 7, "text": "Search for existing trademarks."}]}, {"question": "Name at least 4 kind of products.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Physical products"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Services"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Persons"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Places"}, {"index": 5, "text": "Organizations"}, {"index": 6, "text": "Idea"}]}, {"question": "What are the three product levels?", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing- Product", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Core product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Actual product"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Agumented product"}]}], "Marketing mix": [{"question": "What are the Four \"P's\"?", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Product"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Price"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Promo"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Place"}]}, {"question": "In addition to the four P's and the contingencies for the uncontrollables, the Marketing Plan lays out both the ... and ... along with a detailed budget.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "strategic plan"}, {"index": 2, "text": "tactical plan"}]}, {"question": "The Marketing Plan covers the controllables while also suggesting contingencies for the uncontrollables. Name at least 4 uncontrollables variables.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 4, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "social cultural"}, {"index": 2, "text": "ethical"}, {"index": 3, "text": "technological"}, {"index": 4, "text": "competitive"}, {"index": 5, "text": "political-legal"}, {"index": 6, "text": "economic"}]}, {"question": "... consist of the policies regarding competitive upgrades, reseller pricing, discounts, list price, distributor and street price.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Price"}]}, {"question": "The ... refers to placement such as having the product available where and when targeted customers want to buy it.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Place"}]}, {"question": "The ... refers to the service or tangible good that satisfies the target customer's wants.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Product"}]}, {"question": "To ensure that the marketing mix is managed, it is essential to develop a ... which is formalized in a Marketing Plan.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Marketing strategy"}]}, {"question": "... includes Advertising, PR, Event Marketing, Online Marketing, Direct Marketing, Personal Selling, Channel Marketing and Alliances.", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Promotion"}]}, {"question": "Define \"Marketing Strategy\".", "status": "approved", "category": "Marketing mix", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 1, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "a broad plan for using an organization's resources to meet its marketing objectives"}]}], "Price and Promo": [{"question": "If a company has more than one distribution channel at the same time, than it is named ...", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "multi channel distribution"}]}, {"question": "What does \"cross-benefits pricing\" means?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Set the price for a product below the costs, but higher the price for another product which serves as a direct complement. (e.g. film and camera)"}]}, {"question": "Direct observation, mail surveys, interviews are examples for ...?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Consumer research"}]}, {"question": "Free sources for secondary research are ..?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Public sources"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Commercial sources"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Educational institutions"}]}, {"question": "Name all 3 fields of market research!", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Customer (consumer)"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Competitors (market)"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Product"}]}, {"question": "In ... you gather data and information at colleges and/or universities.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Educational institutions"}]}, {"question": "Open-ended research to define specific problem in market research is called ...?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Exploratory research"}]}, {"question": "Economic status, laws and environmental aspects are ... for the decision between a direct or an indirect distribution.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "environment related factors"}]}, {"question": "Name 2 components of a pricing program!", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Pricing objectives"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Pricing strategies"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Pricing structure"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Price levels"}]}, {"question": "Complexity, transportability and value of a product are ... for the decision between a direct or an indirect distribution.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "product related factors"}]}, {"question": "Public sources, commercial sources and educational institutions are sources of ... ?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Secondary research (of market research)"}]}, {"question": "Market research in case of customers is called ... ?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Consumer research"}]}, {"question": "Name 2 pricing objectives!", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Market share"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Return on investment"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Sales growth"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Maximize long-run profit"}]}, {"question": "... is precise in scope and is used to solve a problem that exploratory research has identified.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Specific research"}]}, {"question": "Name 3 factors that are important for the decision between a direct or an indirect distribution!", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "product related"}, {"index": 2, "text": "customer related"}, {"index": 3, "text": "competition related"}, {"index": 4, "text": "company related"}, {"index": 5, "text": "distribution agent related"}, {"index": 6, "text": "environment related"}]}, {"question": "A perfect price differentiation is only achievable, if ... (name 2 answers)", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "The individual price a customer would pay is known."}, {"index": 2, "text": "It is possible to offer personalized prices."}, {"index": 3, "text": "Resale is forbidden."}]}, {"question": "Quantitative price differentiation means ...?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "The price is connected to the amount of products per customer."}]}, {"question": "In market research are different types of data, which one is the mostly used?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Primary"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Secondary"}, {"index": 3, "text": "Tertiary"}, {"index": 4, "text": "Quaternary"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Secondary"}]}, {"question": "The ... is a tool for communicating with customers and influencing the way they buy.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "price"}]}, {"question": "Parity pricing is choosing a price roughly equivalent to ...?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "the major competition's price"}, {"index": 2, "text": "the costs"}, {"index": 3, "text": "the price your manager says"}, {"index": 4, "text": "the highest price the customer is willing to pay"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "the major competition's price"}]}, {"question": "Amount of customers, dispersal of customer and demand are ... for the decision between a direct or an indirect distribution.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "fillIn", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "customer related factors"}]}, {"question": "Explain the word \"distribution channel\"!", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "A distribution channel describes a product's way from the producer to the customer"}]}, {"question": "Market-based and cost-based are?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Pricing strategies"}]}, {"question": "Partitioning means seperating customers in groups of different ...", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "willingness to pay"}]}, {"question": "What does MSRP stands for?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "manufacturer's suggested retail price"}]}, {"question": "Name 3 company related factors for the decision between a direct or an indirect distribution.", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 3, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 3, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "size of the company"}, {"index": 2, "text": "revenue"}, {"index": 3, "text": "current distribution channels"}, {"index": 4, "text": "assortment of goods"}]}, {"question": "In exploratory research interviews are unstructured in contrast to specific research, but which of these two is more expensive?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [{"index": 1, "text": "Exploratory research"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Specific research"}, {"index": 3, "text": "none of them"}], "type": "multipleChoice", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 2, "text": "Specific research"}]}, {"question": "Who typically sets the price?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 2, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "The product manager"}]}, {"question": "What is floor pricing?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Just covering the costs"}]}, {"question": "What are the names of the different types of data market research involves?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "list", "requiredAnswers": 2, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Primary"}, {"index": 2, "text": "Secondary"}]}, {"question": "Change a price related to time is called ...?", "status": "approved", "category": "Price and Promo", "difficulty": 1, "possibilities": [], "type": "wildcard", "requiredAnswers": 0, "answers": [{"index": 1, "text": "Time-related price differentiation"}]}]}}